Guide to the CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records, 1857-2010 AIS.1991.16
ULS Archives & Special Collections
CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records
1857-2010
ULS Archives & Special Collections
CONSOL Energy Inc
AIS.1991.16
795.34 Linear Feet (305 boxes, 369 tubes, 41 map case drawers, 68 map shelves)
The CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records contains coal mine maps, related documents and topographical information, as well as surface maps and detailed information on mine accidents. Additionally, there are technical drawings, outside notes on multiple mines, traverse and survey books, information on companies and railroads with which CONSOL conducted business, and a variety of non-print materials including photographs, negatives and aperture cards. Digital reproductions of selected material are available online.
Access Restrictions
Series XV (Hardback Maps) records may need to be humidified prior to handling. Please contact Archives & Special Collections at least three business days in advance to ensure items can be safely unrolled and handled.
Series XXIII boxes 303 and 304 are an extension of the case file and restricted to use by Archives & Special Collections faculty and staff.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into 22 series:
Series I. Harmar Mine Maps, 1918-1980
Series II. Oakmont Mine Maps, 1919-1966
Series III. Renton Mine Maps, 1926-1982
Series IV. Robena Mine Maps, 1948-1990
Series V. Sewickley Mine Maps, 1890s-1920s
Series VI. D, E, and F Sheets, 1899-1930
Series VII. R Sheets, 1940-1956
Series VIII. H Sheets
Series IX. K Sheets
Series X. Numbered Sheets, 1861-1955
Series XI. General Mine Maps, 1876-1989
Series XII. Company Sheets, 1876-1989
Series XIII. Property Maps, 1872-1982
Series XIV. Geographic Maps, 1867-1969
Series XV. Hardback Maps, 1861-1984
Series XVI. Survey Books, 1880s-1990s
Series XVII. Traverse Logs, 1880s-1999s
Series XVIII. Records, 1857-2008
Series XIX. Publications, 1915-2010
Series XX. Quecreek Mine Accident Investigation, 1900-2004
Series XXI. Photographic and Media Materials, 1930s-1970s
Series XXII. Union Coal and Coke Company Maps, 1899-1968
The collection is organized into 23 series:
Harmar Mine Maps, 1918-1980
Oakmont Mine Maps, 1919-1966
Renton Mine Maps, 1926-1982
Robena Mine Maps, 1948-1990
Sewickley Mine Maps, 1890s-1920s
D, E, and F Sheets, 1899-1930
R Sheets, 1940-1956
H Sheets
K Sheets
Numbered Sheets, 1861-1955
General Mine Maps, 1876-1989
Company Sheets, 1876-1989
Property Maps, 1872-1982
Geographic Maps, 1867-1969
Hardback Maps, 1861-1984
Survey Books, 1880s-1990s
Traverse Logs, 1880s-1999s
Records, 1857-2008
Publications, 1915-2010
Quecreek Mine Accident Investigation, 1900-2004
Photographic and Media Materials, 1930s-1970s
Union Coal and Coke Company Maps, 1899-1968
Processing Notes, 1991-2006
History
CONSOL Energy Inc. was first introduced and incorporated by an act of the Maryland legislature on March 1860 as Consolidation Coal Company, but was not fully formed until April 19, 1864. Early in CONSOL's history, transportation of coal proved problematic. The coal was originally transferred by wagon, then by flat-bottom riverboats, and later by railroad. The company collaborated with the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad when a large amount of stock was acquired by the railroad. Two years later, the offices moved from New York to Baltimore.
The company faced internal trouble in the late 1800s due to the company-employed miners going on strike. The strike continued for weeks, with order finally restored by the Maryland Militia. The early 1900s also saw change in the company, when it expanded outside of Maryland into Pennsylvania, West Virginia, Minnesota and Wisconsin, and began to ship coal internationally to Japan.
In 1906, the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad sold its shares to a Baltimore syndicate. This was the first attempt by a railroad to relinquish control of the commodities it transported because of investigation by the Interstate Commerce Commission, which examined the relationships between coal-carrying railroads and the companies having mines on their lines. CONSOL continued to prosper in the early 1900s when it expanded into Kentucky and continued to ship coal all over the world during World War I. The company was able to move its offices back to New York in 1921, and by 1925, the company had become the largest commercial producer of bituminous coal in the United States.
The mergers and reorganizations continued when the company restructured its departments in 1927 to increase efficiency. During the early 1930s and the Depression era, the company again had to reorganize and went into receivership after serious financial trouble befell them, but due to their efforts the company was able to emerge from those years on solid footing.
The year 1934 was the company's seventieth anniversary. They owned 300,000 acres of land containing reserves of 1,800,000,000 tons of coal and operated 22 mines in Maryland, Pennsylvania, West Virginia and Kentucky. The years following World War II saw more mergers and the purchasing of other companies. This is also when CONSOL began to develop new breakthroughs in the coal industry.
In 1945, the company merged with Pittsburgh Coal Company and was renamed the Pittsburgh Consolidation Coal Company. One improvement in 1947 was the creation of "Disco," which became a registered trademark of CONSOL. "Disco" was a smokeless solid fuel, and the coal gasification project became a major endeavor of the company. In 1948, the company developed and built a pilot plant for refining tar from a carbonization process.
In 1951, sufficient data became available to prove to CONSOL that it was economical to transport coal by pipeline. In 1956, CONSOL bought the Pocahontas Fuel Company Incorporated, which had reserves and production facilities of low-volatile coal. These fuels were ideal for coking, which was an important ingredient in the manufacture of steel, and a new venture for the coal company. Two years later, the company shortened its name to Consolidation Coal Company.
A major breakthrough for the company occurred in coal pipelining in 1961 with the creation of coal slurry. Coal slurry, a mixture of coal and water, could be pumped for hundreds of miles through a pipeline, distributed by barge, and stored indefinitely in tanks or ponds. This development was hailed as being one of the most important discoveries in fuel transportation and consumption in the past forty years. In 1963, the company contracted with the Office of Coal Research to develop, construct and operate a coal-to-gasoline pilot plant.
The company celebrated 100 years of operation in 1964. Almost 100 billion tons of coal had been mined and CONSOL was still one of the leading producers of coal in the world, with international holdings as well as successful mines located in various states.
In 1966, just two years after the company marked its centennial, Consolidation Coal was acquired by the Continental Oil Company (Conoco). This was part of a general trend whereby U.S. oil companies extended their reach by acquiring coal reserves and large coal producers. In turn, Conoco was acquired by E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company in 1981. This purchase was motivated by DuPont's desire to obtain better control of chemical feedstocks in an era of high oil prices. Consolidation Coal was not a major factor in the Conoco acquisition and did not really fit into DuPont's strategy, especially after coal and oil prices declined. As a result, it was quickly sold off when DuPont was restructured a decade later.
In 1991, a new holding company, CONSOL Energy Inc., was incorporated as a joint venture of DuPont Energy Company and the German energy conglomerate Rheinisch-Westfalisches Elektrizitatswerk A.G., through its wholly owned subsidiaries Rheinbraun A.G. and Rheinbraun U.S.A. GmbH. Consolidation Coal Company became a wholly-owned subsidiary of CONSOL Energy Inc. DuPont eventually sold most of its half interest, so that by 1998, Rheinbraun affiliates owned 94% of CONSOL Energy stock, while DuPont Energy retained only 6%. CONSOL Energy purchased the entire stock of the Rochester & Pittsburgh Coal Company on September 22, 1998. CONSOL Energy stock began trading on the New York Stock Exchange under the symbol "CNX" in 1999, with an initial public offering of more than 20 million shares.
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains maps, information sheets, technical drawings and other records relating primarily to the southwestern Pennsylvania mining activities of CONSOL Energy, Inc. Additionally, there are property maps, plans of lots and drawings of other surface features, plans of structures related to mines owned and operated by CONSOL Energy and its partnering companies. There are also atlases, maps, technical drawings, information sheets, reports, publications, etc. produced in conjunction with or to be used with the mine maps, and non-print materials including photographs, negatives, slides and aperture cards.
Previous Citation
CONSOL Energy, Inc. Mine Maps and Records, 1857-2010, AIS.1991.16, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Consolidation Coal Co. Coal Mine Maps Collection, AIS 91:16.
Separated Material
Box 214 was deaccessioned and transferred to the Beall Archives at Frostburg State University. Please contact that institution directly to view those records
The following records have been separated to create the CONSOL Energy Inc. West Virginia and Eastern Ohio Mine Maps and Records Collection, 1880-1994 (AIS.2004.22):
Box 1 Folders 9-18
Box 2
Box 3
Box 32 Folders 16-19
Box 33
Box 34
Box 35
Box 36
Box 37 Folders 1-4
Box 93 Folder 13
Box 94 Folders 8 and 11
Box 103 Folders 9-10
Box 137 Folder 3
Box 138
Box 139
Box 194 Folders 3-6
Box 195 Folder 1
Box 210 Folders 1-19, 21-28
Box 212 Folder 13
Box 230 Folders 46-49
Box 231 Folders 1 and 17
Box 232
Accruals
Additional material received in 1997, 1998, 2001, 2002, 2004, 2009, 2010, 2011, 2012 and 2013. Further accruals are expected.
Acquisition Information
Gift of CONSOL Energy Inc., beginning in 1991.
Existence and Location of Copies
Digital reproductions of a portion of the photographs in the collection are available electronically at http://historicpittsburgh.org/collection/consol-energy-inc-mine-maps-records. Digital images of surface properties in relation to coal mines from the Monongahela River Consolidated Coal and Coke Company are available in Series XVIII. Records. The I-Tracings (#5000-9999) from this same series were digitized and released online in January 2013 as were the annual reports published by the Pittsburgh Coal Company (1940-1945). CONSOL News and CONSOL Energy News were digitized and released online in December 2013. As part of a multi-year grant project partnering with the Pennsylvania Department of Environmental Protection and the Office of Surface Mining, the hardback maps were digitized and the images are available on the PA Mine Map Atlas here: http://www.paminemaps.psu.edu. Metadata pertaining to each image is available on a DEP website called the Pennsylvania Historic Underground Mine Map Inventory System (PHUMMIS) here: http://www.phummis.pa.gov/phummis/.
Related Material
CONSOL Energy Inc. West Virginia and Eastern Ohio Mine Maps and records Collection, 1880-1994, AIS.2004.22, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Consolidation Coal Company Records, 1854-1971, AIS.2011.03, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Land use maps; Land use -- Pennsylvania, Southwestern -- Maps; Greene County (Pa.) -- Maps; Floor plans; Fayette County (Pa.) -- Maps; Environment; Coal mines and mining -- Pennsylvania, Southwestern -- Maps; Cadastral maps; Business and Industry; Blueprints (Reprographic copies); Beaver County (Pa.) -- Maps; Aperture cards; Allegheny County (Pa.) -- Maps; Ledgers (Account books); Logs (records); Mine maps; Negatives (Photographic); Pennsylvania, Southwestern -- Maps; Photographs; Real property -- Pennsylvania, Southwestern -- Maps; Slides (Photographs); Somerset County (Pa.) -- Maps; Technical drawings; Washington County (Pa.) -- Maps; Westmoreland County (Pa.) -- Maps; Consolidation Coal Company; CONSOL Energy Inc; Pittsburgh Coal Company
- Harmar Mine Maps, 1915-1980; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series includes maps, information sheets, and technical drawings relating to the Harmar Mine. The Harmar Mine was located in Harmarville, Harmar Township, Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, along Guys Run and the Allegheny River on the Pennsylvania Railroad and Harmar Bridge Canal. The mine was first owned by the Harmar Coal Company (beginning ca. 1915) then by the Consumer Coal Company.
  - Index Map, Sheets 1-10 (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - Sheets 11-20 (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 2)
  - Sheets 21-28 (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 3)
  - Sheets 30-40 (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
  - Sheets 41-52 (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 5)
  - Sheets 53-63 (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 6)
  - Property Maps (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 7)
  - Technical Drawings (Map-case 30, Drawer 8, Folder 8)
- Oakmont Mine Maps, 1919-1966; II.
  This series includes maps, information sheets, and technical drawings relating to the Oakmont Mine, also known as the Barking Mine. It was located in Barking, Plum Township, Allegheny County, Pennsylvania, along a strip of land under the cliffs of Coxcomb hill on the Allegheny Valley Railroad and with barge loading facilities on the Allegheny River. The mine was owned by the Diamond Coal and Coke Company, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
  - Index Map, Sheets 1-5 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 1)
  - Sheets 1-26 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 2)
  - Sheets 8-14 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 3)
  - Sheets 26-84 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 4)
  - Sheets 301-309, Aerial Sheets 1-6 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 5)
  - Technical Drawings (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 6)
  - Oakmont Mine, 1971 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 6A)
- Renton Mine Maps, 1926-1982; III.
  This series includes maps, information sheets, and technical drawings relating to the Renton Mine located in Renton, Plum Township, Allegheny County, Pennsylvania. The mine was owned by Union Collieries Company, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
  - Index Map, Sheets 1-15 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 7)
  - Sheets 16-25 (Map-case 1, Drawer 2, Folder 8)
  - Sheets 28-73 (Map-case 30, Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - Sheets 79-103, Aerial Sheets 1-5 (Map-case 30, Drawer 9, Folder 2)
  - Technical Drawings (Map-case 30, Drawer 9, Folder 3-5)
- Robena Mine Maps, 1948-1990; IV.
  This series includes maps and information sheets relating to the Robena Mine located in Carmichaels, Monongahela Township, Greene County, Pennsylvania. The mine was owned by United States Steel Corporation, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.
  - Index Map, Sheets 304-329 (Map-case 30, Drawer 9, Folder 6)
  - Sheets 330-338 (Map-case 30, Drawer 9, Folder 7)
  - Sheets 342-349 (Map-case 30, Drawer 9, Folder 8)
  - Sheets 350-354 (Map-case 30, Drawer 9, Folder 9)
  - Sheets 360-366 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - Sheets 367-372 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 2)
  - Sheets 373-387 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 3)
  - Sheets 388-404 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 4)
  - Sheets 405-410 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 5)
  - Sheets 411-415 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 6)
  - Sheets 427-434 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 7)
  - Sheets 435-451 (Map-case 30, Drawer 10, Folder 8)
  - Sheets 452-459 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 1)
  - Sheets 460-475 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 2)
  - Sheets 476-481 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 3)
  - Sheets 494-501 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 4)
  - Sheets 502-520 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 5)
  - Sheets 521-529 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 6)
  - Sheets 548-553 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 7)
  - Sheets 575-613 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 8)
  - Sheets 50, 54-56, 58-60, 64-66 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 9)
- Sewickley Mine Maps, 1890s-1920s; V.
  This series includes maps and information sheets related to the Sewickley Mine. The Sewickley Mine was a slope mine located in Arona, Hempfield Township, Westmoreland County, Pennsylvania, on the Little Sewickley Creek, half a mile east of Herminie, on the north side of the Pennsylvania Railroad tracks. The mine was owned by Sewickley Gas and Coal Company, Greensburg, Pennsylvania (ca. 1898-1902), then by the Keystone Coal and Coke Company, Greensburg, Pennsylvania (ca. 1903-1920). The Sewickley Mine was merged with Keystone Mine Shaft on June 1, 1920.
  - Sheets 448-524 (Map-case 30, Drawer 11, Folder 10)
- D, E, and F Sheets, 1899-1930; VI.
  This series of technical drawings includes plans of air shafts and other structures related to mines. D sheets measure 14" x 20"; E sheets measure 20.25" x 29.5"; and F sheets measure 29" x 42.25".
  - D 10314 & 10556, E 10001-10857 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - F 5000-5075 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - F 10006-10578 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - F 10579-10704 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - F 10705-10828 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - F 10839-10909 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 6)
  - F 10910-11010 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 7)
  - F 11011-11131 (Map-case 1, Drawer 6, Folder 8)
- R Sheets, 1940-1956; VII.
  This series includes maps of Pittsburgh Coal Company mine works under or near Pennsylvania state highways.
  - R 1-10 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - R 15-28 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - R 33-64 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - R 66-107 (Map-case 1, Drawer 7, Folder 4)
- H Sheets, 1900-1980s; VIII.
  This series includes maps of mine workings on specially treated linen sheets that measure 42" x 60". The sheets largely reflect the mining operations of the Pittsburgh Coal Company, and later the Pittsburgh Consolidation Coal Company.
  - Index Maps of H & K Sheets- Maps 1-6 (3 copies of each) (Map-case 1, Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - H 5002-5009 (Map-case 1, Drawer 8, Folder 2)
  - H 5010-5019 (Map-case 1, Drawer 8, Folder 3)
  - H 5020-5029 (Map-case 1, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
  - H 5030-5032, 5034, 5039 (Map-case 1, Drawer 8, Folder 5)
  - H 5040-5048 (Map-case 1, Drawer 8, Folder 6)
  - H 5050-5057, 5059 (Map-case 1, Drawer 8, Folder 7)
  - H 5060-5069 (Map-case 1, Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - H 5070-5074, 5079 (Map-case 1, Drawer 9, Folder 2)
  - H 5080-5089 (Map-case 1, Drawer 9, Folder 3)
  - H 5090-5094, 5096-5097, 5099 (Map-case 1, Drawer 9, Folder 4)
  - H 5100-5101, 5104-5105, 5107, 5109 (Map-case 1, Drawer 9, Folder 5)
  - H 5110-5113, 5115-5119 (Map-case 1, Drawer 9, Folder 6)
  - H 5120-5129 (Map-case 1, Drawer 9, Folder 7)
  - H 5130-5132, 5136-5138 (Map-case 1, Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - H 5140- 5141, 5143-5144, 5146-5149 (Map-case 1, Drawer 10, Folder 2)
  - H 5150-5159 (Map-case 1, Drawer 10, Folder 3)
  - H 5160- 5163, 5165-5168 (Map-case 1, Drawer 10, Folder 4)
  - H 5171-5175, 5177-5178 (Map-case 1, Drawer 10, Folder 5)
  - H 5180-5188 (Map-case 1, Drawer 10, Folder 6)
  - H 5190-5192, 5194-5198 (Map-case 1, Drawer 11, Folder 1)
  - H 5200, 5202-5209 (Map-case 1, Drawer 11, Folder 2)
  - H 5210-5219 (Map-case 1, Drawer 11, Folder 3)
  - H 5220-5221, 5223-5225, 5227-5229 (Map-case 1, Drawer 11, Folder 4)
  - H 5230-5239 (Map-case 1, Drawer 11, Folder 5)
  - H 5240, 5242-5246 (Map-case 1, Drawer 12, Folder 1)
  - H 5252-5254, 5256-5259 (Map-case 1, Drawer 12, Folder 2)
  - H 5260-5269 (Map-case 1, Drawer 12, Folder 3)
  - H 5270-5273, 5275-5279 (Map-case 1, Drawer 12, Folder 4)
  - H 5280-5289 (Map-case 1, Drawer 12, Folder 5)
  - H 5290-5299 (Map-case 1, Drawer 13, Folder 1)
  - H 5300-5309 (Map-case 1, Drawer 13, Folder 2)
  - H 5310-5319 (Map-case 1, Drawer 13, Folder 3)
  - H 5320-5329 (Map-case 1, Drawer 13, Folder 4)
  - H 5330-5339 (Map-case 1, Drawer 13, Folder 5)
  - H 5340-5346, 5348-5349 (Map-case 1, Drawer 14, Folder 1)
  - H 5350, 5352-5359 (Map-case 1, Drawer 14, Folder 2)
  - H 5360-5368 (Map-case 1, Drawer 14, Folder 3)
  - H 5371, 5373-5374, 5376-5378 (Map-case 1, Drawer 14, Folder 4)
  - H 5383-5388 (Map-case 1, Drawer 14, Folder 5)
  - H 5391-5394, 5396, 5398-5399 (Map-case 1, Drawer 15, Folder 1)
  - H 5400-5401, 5403-5407, 5409 (Map-case 1, Drawer 15, Folder 2)
  - H 5412-5418, 5423-5429 (Map-case 1, Drawer 15, Folder 3)
  - H 5430-5439 (Map-case 1, Drawer 15, Folder 4)
  - H 5440-5447 (Map-case 1, Drawer 15, Folder 5)
- K Sheets, 1900-1980s; IX.
  This series includes maps of mine workings on specially treated linen sheets that measure 30.5" x 42.5". The sheets largely reflect the mining operations of the Pittsburgh Coal Company, and later the Pittsburgh Consolidation Coal Company.
  - K 5001-5010 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1, Folder 1)
  - K 5011-5020 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1, Folder 2)
  - K 5021-5030 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1, Folder 3)
  - K 5031-5040 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1, Folder 4)
  - K 5041-5050 (Map-case 2, Drawer 1, Folder 5)
  - K 5051-5060 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2, Folder 1)
  - K 5061-5070 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2, Folder 2)
  - K 5071-5080 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2, Folder 3)
  - K 5081-5090 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2, Folder 4)
  - K 5091-5100 (Map-case 2, Drawer 2, Folder 5)
  - K 5101-5110 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3, Folder 1)
  - K 5111-5120 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3, Folder 2)
  - K 5121-5130 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3, Folder 3)
  - K 5132-5140 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3, Folder 4)
  - K 5141-5150 (Map-case 2, Drawer 3, Folder 5)
  - K 5151-5158 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4, Folder 1)
  - K 5169-5180 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4, Folder 2)
  - K 5181-5195 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4, Folder 3)
  - K 5196-5210 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4, Folder 4)
  - K 5211-5220 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4, Folder 5)
  - K 5221-5229 (Map-case 2, Drawer 4, Folder 6)
  - K 5234-5243 (Map-case 2, Drawer 5, Folder 1)
  - K 5250-5253, 5256-5260 (Map-case 2, Drawer 5, Folder 2)
  - K 5261-5270 (Map-case 2, Drawer 5, Folder 3)
  - K 5271-5284 (Map-case 2, Drawer 5, Folder 4)
  - K 5288-5289, 5292-5297, 5301-5305 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6, Folder 1)
  - K 5306-5319 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6, Folder 2)
  - K 5320-5330 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6, Folder 3)
  - K 5331-5340 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6, Folder 4)
  - K 5341-5346, 5348, 5353-5355 (Map-case 2, Drawer 6, Folder 5)
  - K 5356-5359, 5362-5365 (Map-case 2, Drawer 7, Folder 1)
  - K 5366-5379 (Map-case 2, Drawer 7, Folder 2)
  - K 5380-5390 (Map-case 2, Drawer 7, Folder 3)
  - K 5391-5400 (Map-case 2, Drawer 7, Folder 4)
  - K 5401-5409 (Map-case 2, Drawer 7, Folder 5)
  - K 5414-5425 (Map-case 2, Drawer 8, Folder 1)
  - K 5426-5437 (Map-case 2, Drawer 8, Folder 2)
  - K 5438-5449 (Map-case 2, Drawer 8, Folder 3)
  - K 5450-5461, 5464-5465 (Map-case 2, Drawer 8, Folder 4)
  - K 5468-5480 (Map-case 2, Drawer 8, Folder 5)
  - K 5481-5491 (Map-case 2, Drawer 9, Folder 1)
  - K 5492-5498 (Map-case 2, Drawer 9, Folder 2)
  - K 5501-5509 (Map-case 2, Drawer 9, Folder 3)
  - K 5510-5520 (Map-case 2, Drawer 9, Folder 4)
  - K 5521-5527, 5530 (Map-case 2, Drawer 9, Folder 5)
  - K 5531-5540 (Map-case 2, Drawer 10, Folder 1)
  - K 5541-5545, 5553-5556 (Map-case 2, Drawer 10, Folder 2)
  - K 5561-5564, 5566-5570 (Map-case 2, Drawer 10, Folder 3)
  - K 5571-5576, 5579-5582 (Map-case 2, Drawer 10, Folder 4)
  - K 5586, 5595-5597, 5599-5600, 5610, 5616-5617 (Map-case 2, Drawer 10, Folder 5)
  - K 5701-5710 (filed in Map-case 1, Drawer 8) (Map-case 2, Drawer 10, Folder 6)
  - K 5711-5720 (Map-case 2, Drawer 10, Folder 7)
  - K 5721-5730 (Map-case 2, Drawer 11, Folder 1)
  - K 5731-5736, 5801-5802, 5804-5805 (Map-case 2, Drawer 11, Folder 2)
  - K 5806-5819 (Map-case 2, Drawer 11, Folder 3)
  - K 5820-5830 (Map-case 2, Drawer 11, Folder 4)
  - K 5831-5840 (Map-case 2, Drawer 11, Folder 5)
  - K 5841-5850 (Map-case 2, Drawer 11, Folder 6)
  - K 5851-5860 (Map-case 2, Drawer 11, Folder 7)
  - K 5861-5874 (Map-case 2, Drawer 12, Folder 1)
  - K 5875-5889 (Map-case 2, Drawer 12, Folder 2)
  - K 5890-5899 (Map-case 2, Drawer 12, Folder 3)